

# Hi! I'm OLEKSII DONIN

⊙ Kiev, Ukraine☐ 10th march 1986

← +38 096 3 838 460☑ oleksii.donin@gmail.com

Digital Banner Ad Developer; Digital Designer/Developer; Motion Design;

- oleksiidonin.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/oleksii-donin/
- behance.net/oleksiidonin

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a professional digital designer/ developer from Ukraine with more than fifteen years of digital experience. My main specialization is banner ads development. I can create Rich Media ads and HTML5, AMP HTML, and GIF animated standard banner ads. I also have strong motion design, web/digital design, and front-end web development skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

Creative Practice (2021 — 2022)

- Web Design Basics
- Design Basics
- Figma Basics
- After Effects Basics

# Priazovskiy State Technical

**University** (2003 — 2008)

 Automation of technological processes and manufactures

# **EXPERIENCE**

10.2008 — till now

# Freelance digital designer/developer

worked as freelancer with Ukrainian branches of Publicis, Universal McCann, Philip Morris International, Havas Group, Mediacom, Twiga Ukraine, BBDO and many others.

05.2008 — 10.2008

#### **Handmade Interactive Ltd**

Front-end web developer

03.2007 — 04.2008

#### **Mariupolcity Ltd**

Adobe Flash developer

### SOFTWARE

Adobe Animate

Google Web Designer

Adobe Photoshop

Figma

Adobe Illustrator

# CODING

AMPHTML

CSS3

JavaScript

**Action Script 3** 

### **HARD SKILLS**

Banner ads production

Motion design

Web / digital design

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Time management
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem-solving
- Creativity
- Openness to criticism
- Critical thinking
- Resourcefulness

#### LANGUAGES

Ukrainian

English

Russian

## **INTERESTS**

Front end developmetn

- Travel
- Ecotourism
- Modern art
- Design
- Architecture